{
  "info": {
    "name": "Binary Quiz",
    "questions": 10
  },
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is binary?",
      "answers": [
        "A sequence of 1s and 0s",
        "The way a computer speaks",
        "A useless code that is no longer used"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of 'base' system is binary known as?",
      "answers": ["Base 10", "Base 2", "Base 16"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of number system is used in everyday life?",
      "answers": ["Denary", "Binary", "A simple number system"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What would the denary number 199 be in binary?",
      "answers": ["11000110", "10100111", "11000111"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What would the denary number 55 be in binary?",
      "answers": ["00110111", "00101111", "01010111"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What would the denary number 222 be in binary?",
      "answers": ["11010110", "10111110", "11011110"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What would 10110010 be as a denary number?",
      "answers": ["168", "178", "188"],
      "correctAnswer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "What would 00101110 be as a denary number?",
      "answers": ["46", "36", "56"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What would 00100101 + 01000100 be as a binary number?",
      "answers": ["10101001", "01101001", "01101011"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an overflow error?",
      "answers": [
        "When the result of a binary calculation is too long for a computer to process",
        "When something is spelt incorrectly when programming",
        "When the computer program has been given the wrong command"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
